





### Summary

Jump to Section

Result-oriented Professional with over 3 years of experience in Business Analysis, Project Management, System Analysis, Data Management, Data Mining, Data Modeling, Process Improvement, Database Development, Client Management, Python, Research process in primary & secondary.

## **Work Experience**

Liquidhub Technology, Capgemini Group Pvt. Ltd. as Sr. Data Analyst Apr 2017 to Oct 2019

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Interpret data from primary and secondary research using statistical techniques and provide ongoing reports.

Compile and validate data, reinforce and maintain compliance with corporate standards. Presented data and conclusions to team in order to improve strategies and operations. Working with managing leadership to prioritize business and information requirements.

- LiquidHub as Senior Analyst May 2016 to Till Date
- Annik Technology Pvt. Ltd. as Data Analyst May 2016 to Apr 2017

Optimized data collection procedures and generated reports on a weekly, monthly & quarterly basis.

Used advanced Microsoft Excel to create pivot tables as well as VLOOKUP function. Develop and initiate more efficient data collection procedures.

^ Back to Top

### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Computers) from shri ram murti womens college of engineering & technology in 2014

^ Back to Top

### IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience Python

## **Important**

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

1 341011		
MS SQL		
EXCEL		
OOPS		
SDLC		

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

^ Back to Top

### **Affirmative Action**

### **Work Authorization**

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.